{"data":[{"question":"A baby is under parental ________.","a":"guidance","b":"guide","c":"guided","d":"guideless","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adj + Noun.\u00a0\n- Guidance(n): help and advice that is given to someone about their work, education, or personal life.\u00a0\nunder somebody's expert guidance.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Uranus is just ________ to be seen on a clear night with the naked eye.","a":"bright enough","b":"enough brightly","c":"as enough bright","d":"bright as enough","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adjective + enough to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"Before Alexander Fleming discovered penicillin, many people died ________.","a":"infected with simple bacteria","b":"from simple bacterial infections","c":"infections were simple bacteria","d":"infecting of simple bacteria","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Die of\/from: reasons lead to death.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"That most natural time units are not simple multiples of each other ________ in constructing a calendar.","a":"it is a primary problem","b":"is a primary problem","c":"a primary problem is","d":"a primary problem","answer":"2","explain":"- The subject (That most.....each other) + singular verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"________ the plow is being displaced by new techniques that protect the land and promise more abundant crops.","a":"As a whole","b":"Wholly","c":"On a whole","d":"The whole","answer":"1","explain":"\n- As a whole: used to say that all the parts of something are being considered together.\u00a0\n- On the whole: used to say that something is generally true.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"In excess of 80 percent of the UN's budget is used ________ The economic development of member nations.","a":"support","b":"supporting","c":"the support","d":"to support","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be used to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The bacteria in milk is destroyed when ________ to at least 62\u00b0C.","a":"it be heated","b":"it heated","c":"it is heated","d":"it will be heated","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice of simple present: Be + PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"In order for people who spoke different languages to engage in trade ________, they often developed a simplified language called \"pidgin\".","a":"with each the other","b":"with each to the other","c":"with each another","d":"with each other","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Engage with sbd\/sth: to get involved with other people and their ideas in order to understand them.\u00a0\n- Each other: used to show that each of two or more people does something to the other.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"The two main ________ are permanent magnets and electromagnets.","a":"kinds of magnets","b":"kind of magnets","c":"kind magnets","d":"kinds magnets","answer":"1","explain":"- We need a plural noun as the subject of the sentence (the two main of kinds of magnets)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"},{"question":"You ought to book in advance. You can't rely ________ a hotel room.","a":"on finding","b":"in finding","c":"of finding","d":"about finding","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Rely on doing something\/something: trust or depend on someone or something to do what you need or expect them to do.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"17","type":"1"}]}